🛑MM Service Rules🛑

🔶 What I do:
- My job is to make sure that your trade completes successfully, and that both parties get what they wanted.
- I will prevent scam attempts during the trade and warn you if I see the trade as high-risk.
- I will guide you through the trade and give you advice on what to do, especially if you are new and it's your first trade.
- I will be available for help after the trade, for no additional fee. Things like how to secure an account, withdraw a payment, tips to prevent scams like account recalls or payment chargeback and help in recovering from a scam.
- I will answer any questions that you might have regarding virtual item trading or about the middleman process, for free and regardless if you plan to use my service or not.
🔶What I don't do:
- Find a buyer for your account/item and/or sell it on your behalf. It is your job to find a buyer.
- Find a seller for the account/item that you are looking to buy.
- I do not buy or sell. Don't offer me your items. I'm also not interested in reselling your items.
- I do not convert payment methods (e.g. Paypal to Skrill). Both buyer and seller must use the same payment method.
- I will not scam people who have scammed you (revenge scam) or participate in any kind of fraud.

🔶Quick guide and trade flow:
A typical middleman transaction goes like this:

1. One party creates and sends a trade request here.
2. The other party gets a message in their inbox where they can accept the offer.
3. Once accepted, a trade is created and a MM will be assigned. Wait until the MM joins.
4. After joining, the MM will instruct the traders on what to do next.
5. MM fee is paid, usually by the buyer ($5 + 6% of the item value)
6. Seller provides the account/item to the MM
7. MM checks whether the account/item matches with what is advertised
8. MM secures the account and gives a green light to the buyer
9. Buyer makes the payment to the seller directly
10. Seller confirms receipt and the item is released to the buyer
11. Buyer confirms item receipt and trade is closed. Feedback can now be exchanged.